Indiana University President's Office records, 1963-1990 C459
Indiana University Archives
- Administrative records, 1963-1990; undated (Box 1)
  - Enrollment Statistics (Box 104)
    - December 1977 (Box 104)
    - August 1977 (Box 104)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 104)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 105)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 105)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 105)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 105)
  - Entertaining Files (Official) (Box 105)
    - January-July, 1971 (Box 105)
    - September-December, 1971 (Box 105)
    - January-June, 1972 (Box 105)
    - A-M, August 1972-July 1973 (Box 105)
    - N-Z, August 1972-July 1973 (Box 105)
    - A-M, August 1973-July 1974 (Box 105)
    - N-Z, August 1973-July 1974 (Box 105)
    - August 1974-December 1974 (Box 105)
    - January 1975-August 1975 (Box 105)
    - A-L, August 1975-July 1976 (Box 105)
    - M-Z, August 1975-July 1976 (Box 105)
    - A-L, August 1976-July 1977 (Box 105)
    - M-Z, August 1976-July 1977 (Box 105)
    - A-L, August 1977-July 1978 (Box 106)
    - M-Z, August 1977-July 1978 (Box 106)
    - A-H, August 1978-June 1979 (Box 106)
    - I-Z, August 1978-June 1979 (Box 106)
    - A-E, July 1979-June 1980 (Box 106)
    - F-M, July 1979-June 1980 (Box 106)
    - N-Z, July 1979-June 1980 (Box 106)
    - A-E, July 1980-July 1981 (Box 106)
    - F-L, July 1980-July 1981 (Box 106)
    - M-R, July 1980-July 1981 (Box 106)
    - S-Z, July 1980-July 1981 (Box 106)
    - A-D, August 1981-June 1982 (Box 106)
    - E-H, August 1981-June 1982 (Box 106)
    - I-P, August 1981-June 1982 (Box 106)
    - Q-Z, August 1981-June 1982 (Box 106)
    - A-B, July 1982-June 1983 (Box 107)
    - C-G, July 1982-June 1983 (Box 107)
    - H-L, July 1982-June 1983 (Box 107)
    - M-N, July 1982-June 1983 (Box 107)
    - O-Z, July 1982-June 1983 (Box 107)
    - A-G, 1983-1984 (Box 107)
    - H-O, 1983-1984 (Box 107)
    - A-C, July 1984-June 1985 (Box 107)
    - D-I, July 1984-June 1985 (Box 107)
    - J-M, July 1984-June 1985 (Box 107)
  - Environmental Health & Safety (Box 107)
    - General, 1972-1985 (Box 107)
    - Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 107)
  - Environmental Studies (Box 107)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 108)
    - 1972-1974 (Box 108)
  - Environmental Systems Applications Center, 1971-1972 (Box 108)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (Box 108)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 108)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 108)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 108)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 108)
    - 1974 (Box 108)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 108)
  - Equipment Lending Policy, 1972 (Box 108)
  - Equitable Life Insurance Society (Box 108)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 108)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 108)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 108)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 108)
  - Ethics, 1973-1974 (Box 108)
  - Europe University, 1971 (Box 108)
  - Evansville, 1986 (Box 108)
  - Evening Classes (Box 108)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 108)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 108)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 108)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 108)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 108)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 108)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 108)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 108)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 108)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 108)
  - Examinations, 1971-1972 (Box 108)
  - Exchange Home, 1971-1972 (Box 108)
  - Executive and Employee Benefit Plans, 1971-1972 (Box 108)
  - Executive Deanship Search and Screen Committee (IUPUI), 1982 (Box 108)
  - Exon, 1980 (Box 108)
  - Exxon Education Foundation, 1973-1974 (Box 108)
  - F (Box 108)
    - 1971-1982 (Box 108)
    - 1983 (Box 108)
    - 1984 (Box 108)
    - 1985 (Box 108)
    - 1986 (Box 108)
    - 1987 (Box 108)
  - Facilities Use Committee (Report of the Public Performance Policies Committee), 1971 (Box 108)
  - Fam, 1971-1987 (Box 108)
  - Fe, 1971-1987 (Box 108)
  - Fen, 1971-1987 (Box 109)
  - Fi, 1971-1987 (Box 109)
  - Fin, 1971-1987 (Box 109)
  - Fl, 1971-1987 (Box 109)
  - Fis, 1971-1987 (Box 109)
  - Fit, 1971-1987 (Box 109)
  - Flo, 1971-1987 (Box 109)
  - Fo, 1971-1987 (Box 109)
  - For, 1971-1987 (Box 109)
  - Fos, 1971-1987 (Box 109)
  - Fr, 1971-1987 (Box 109)
  - Fre, 1971-1987 (Box 109)
  - Fri, 1971-1987 (Box 109)
  - Fro, 1971-1987 (Box 109)
  - Fu, 1971-1987 (Box 109)
  - Fabrychi, William, 1971-1973 (Box 109)
  - Facilities Studies Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 109)
  - Facilities (Box 109)
    - Use (Box 109)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 109)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 109)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 109)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 109)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 109)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 109)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 109)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 109)
    - Assembly Hall (Box 109)
      - 1970-1975 (Box 109)
      - Basketball Tournament, 1971 (Box 109)
      - Pacers, 1972 (Box 109)
      - Proposed Events, 1974-1977 (Box 109)
      - Ushers, 1975 (Box 109)
    - Athletics (Box 109)
      - Fieldhouse (Box 109)
        - 1973 (Box 109)
        - 1978 (Box 109)
      - Wildermuth, 1973 (Box 109)
    - Film Policies, 1975 (Box 109)
    - Pop Concerts, 1974 (Box 109)
    - Residence Halls, 1971 (Box 109)
    - Safety Department, 1974 (Box 109)
    - Stadium 10th Street, 1972-1975 (Box 109)
  - Fact File (News Bureau), 1979-1980 (Box 109)
  - Faculty (Box 109)
    - General (Box 109)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 109)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 110)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 110)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 110)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 110)
      - 1976 (Box 110)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 110)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 110)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 110)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 110)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 110)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 110)
      - 1982 (Box 110)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 110)
      - 1983 (Box 110)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 110)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 110)
      - 1984 (Box 110)
      - 1985 (Box 110)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 110)
      - 1986 (Box 110)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 110)
    - Abroad, 1971-1972 (Box 110)
    - Appointments (Box 110)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 110)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 110)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 110)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 110)
    - Bibliography (Box 110)
      - 1970-1971 (Box 110)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 110)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 110)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 110)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 110)
    - Collective Bargaining (Box 110)
      - 1975 (Box 110)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 110)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 110)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 110)
    - Concerned Title Professors, 1980-1981 (Box 110)
    - Constitution (Box 110)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 111)
      - 1972-1974 (Box 111)
      - 1974-1976 (Box 111)
      - 1976-1978 (Box 111)
      - 1984 (Box 111)
    - Course Evaluations (Box 111)
      - 1972-1983 (Box 111)
      - 1971 (Box 111)
    - Distinguished Name Professor (Box 111)
      - 1975-1976, (2 folders) (Box 111)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 111)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 111)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 111)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 111)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 111)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 111)
      - 1981-1984 (Box 111)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 111)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 111)
      - 1985 (Box 111)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 111)
    - Emeritus Titles, 1973-1976 (Box 111)
    - Faculty Council (Bloomington) (Box 111)
      - General (Box 111)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 111)
        - 1972 (Box 111)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 111)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 111)
        - 1974 (Box 111)
        - 1975 (Box 111)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 111)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 111)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 111)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 111)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 111)
        - 1980 (Box 111)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 111)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 111)
        - 1982 (Box 111)
        - 1982-1983 (Box 111)
        - 1981-1983 (Box 111)
        - 1983 (Box 111)
        - 1979-1983 (Box 111)
        - 1984 (Box 111)
        - 1985 (Box 111)
        - 1986-1987 (Box 111)
      - Committees (Box 111)
        - 1969-1972 (Box 111)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 111)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 111)
        - 1979-1981 (Box 111)
      - Memoranda and Correspondence, 1969-1974 (Box 111)
      - Memorial Resolutions (Box 111)
        - General (Box 111)
          - 1971-1972 (Box 111)
          - 1972-1973 (Box 111)
          - 1973-1974 (Box 111)
          - 1974-1975 (Box 111)
          - 1976-1977 (Box 111)
          - 1977-1978 (Box 111)
          - 1978 (Box 111)
        - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 111)
        - Alphabetical (Box 111)
          - 1971-1972 (Box 111)
          - 1972-1973 (Box 111)
          - 1973-1974 (Box 111)
          - 1974-1975 (Box 111)
          - 1974-1975 (Box 111)
          - 1976-1977 (Box 111)
          - 1977-1978 (Box 111)
          - 1977 (Box 111)
          - 1978-1979 (Box 111)
          - 1979-1980 (Box 111)
          - 1981 (Box 112)
          - 1981-1982 (Box 112)
          - 1982-1983 (Box 112)
          - 1983, (3 folders) (Box 112)
          - 1984 (Box 112)
          - 1985 (Box 112)
          - 1986 (Box 112)
          - 1987 (Box 112)
    - Faculty Council (IUPUI), 1984 (Box 112)
    - Faculty Council (University) (Box 112)
      - General (Box 112)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 112)
        - 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 112)
        - 1973-1974, (2 folders) (Box 112)
        - 1975 (Box 112)
        - 1974-1975, (2 folders) (Box 112)
        - 1975-1976, (3 folders) (Box 112)
        - 1976 (Box 112)
        - October 12, 1976 (Box 112)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 112)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 112)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 112)
        - March 28, 1978 (Box 112)
        - October 10, 1978 (Box 112)
        - February 13, 1979 (Box 112)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 112)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 112)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 112)
        - 1982 (Box 310)
        - 1982-1983 (Box 310)
        - October 12, 1982 (Box 310)
        - November 30, 1982 (Box 310)
        - 1983-1984 (Box 310)
        - February 8, 1983 (Box 310)
        - April 26, 1983 (Box 310)
        - 1984 (Box 310)
        - 1985 (Box 310)
        - 1986 (Box 310)
        - 1987 (Box 310)
      - Committees (Box 310)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 310)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 311)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 311)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 311)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 311)
        - 1977-1979 (Box 311)
    - Constitution, 1972-1973 (Box 311)
    - Faculty Handbook (Box 311)
      - 1971-1972, (2 folders) (Box 311)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 311)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 311)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 311)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 311)
    - Faculty - History of Medicine (Proposed), 1974-1975 (Box 311)
    - Leaves of Absence, 1974 (Box 311)
    - Moving Expenses, 1971-1972 (Box 311)
    - Necrology (Box 311)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 311)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 311)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 311)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 311)
    - Promotions (Box 311)
      - 1969-1970 (Box 113)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 113)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 113)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 113)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 113)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 113)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 113)
      - 1987 (Box 113)
    - Publications (Box 113)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 113)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 113)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 113)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 113)
    - Reappointments, 1971-1972 (Box 113)
    - Record Systems (Box 113)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 113)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 113)
    - Records (Box 113)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 113)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 113)
    - Recruitment, 1972-1973 (Box 113)
    - Retirement (Box 113)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 113)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 113)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 113)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 113)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 113)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 113)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 113)
    - Sabbatical Leaves (Box 113)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 113)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 113)
    - Salaries (Box 113)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 113)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 113)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 113)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 113)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 113)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 113)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 113)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 113)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 113)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 113)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 113)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 113)
      - 1986 (Box 113)
    - Summer School Faculty Salaries, 1971-1972 (Box 113)
    - Statistics (Box 113)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 113)
      - 1980 (Box 113)
    - Tenure (Box 113)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 113)
      - 1972 (Box 113)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 113)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 113)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 113)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 113)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 113)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 113)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 113)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 113)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 113)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 113)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 113)
    - Unions (Box 113)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 113)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 113)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 113)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 113)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 113)
    - Women (Box 113)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 113)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 113)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 113)
    - Workload (Box 113)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 113)
      - 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 113)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 113)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 113)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 113)
  - Fall Carnival, 1972 (Box 113)
  - Farmer, Richard N., 1976 (Box 113)
  - FCC Commissioners Meeting, 1988 (Box 113)
  - Fee Remissions (Box 113)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 113)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 113)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 113)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 113)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 113)
    - 1981 (Box 113)
    - 1981-1983 (Box 113)
    - 1986 (Box 113)
    - 1987 (Box 113)
  - Fees (Box 113)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 113)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 113)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 113)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 115)
    - 1973-1975 (Box 115)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 115)
    - 1976 (Box 115)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 115)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 115)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 115)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 115)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 115)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 115)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 115)
    - 1983 (Box 115)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 115)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 115)
    - 1985-1986, (2 folders) (Box 115)
    - 1986 (Box 115)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 115)
  - Fees Collection Policy (Box 115)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 115)
    - 1975, (2 folders) (Box 115)
  - Fees - Out of State Differential, Residency Status (Box 115)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 115)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 115)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 115)
  - Fellowships (Box 115)
    - General (Box 115)
      - 1980, (2 folders) (Box 115)
      - 1982 (Box 115)
      - 1983 (Box 115)
      - 1984 (Box 115)
      - 1985-1986, (2 folders) (Box 115)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 115)
      - 1987 (Box 115)
    - Assistantships (Box 115)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 116)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 116)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 116)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 116)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 116)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 116)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 116)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 116)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 116)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 116)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 116)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 116)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 116)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 116)
    - Fullbright Hayes, 1971-1979 (Box 116)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation (Box 116)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 116)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 116)
  - Fermilab (Box 116)
    - 1982 (Box 116)
    - 1986 (Box 116)
    - 1987 (Box 116)
  - Film Policy, 1977 (Box 116)
  - Films (Box 116)
    - 1971-1987 (Box 116)
    - 1984 (Box 116)
  - Financial Aid Exit Interview, 1979 (Box 116)
  - Financial Report (Box 116)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 116)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 116)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 116)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 116)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 116)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 116)
    - 1979-1981 (Box 116)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 116)
  - Fine Arts (Box 116)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 116)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 116)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 116)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 116)
    - 1975 (Box 116)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 116)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 116)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 116)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 116)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 116)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 116)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 116)
    - 1984 (Box 116)
    - 1985 (Box 116)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 116)
  - Fine Arts Ford Foundation Grant, 1977 (Box 116)
  - Fine Arts Museum (Box 116)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 116)
    - 1972-1974 (Box 116)
    - 1977 (Box 116)
  - Fire Drills, Inspections, 1971-1972 (Box 116)
  - Fiscut, 1984 (Box 117)
  - Focus: The Environment, 1970-1972 (Box 117)
  - Folklore Institute, 1976-1986 (Box 117)
  - Fonda Hayden, 1979-1980 (Box 117)
  - Ford Foundation (Box 117)
    - General (Box 117)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 117)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 117)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 117)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 117)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 117)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 117)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 117)
      - 1978-1980 (Box 117)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 117)
      - 1982 (Box 117)
      - 1983 (Box 117)
    - Annual report, 1970-1971 (Box 117)
  - Foreign Correspondence, 1977 (Box 117)
  - Foreign Student Enrollment and Student Profiles, 1975-1976 (Box 117)
  - Foreign Students (Box 117)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 117)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 117)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 117)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 117)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 117)
    - 1976 (Box 117)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 117)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 117)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 117)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 117)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 117)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 117)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 117)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 117)
  - Foreign Student Advisory, 1976 (Box 117)
  - Foreign Study Centers (Box 117)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 117)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 117)
  - Foreign Visitors (Box 117)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 117)
    - 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 117)
    - 1973-1975 (Box 117)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 117)
    - 1976-1978 (Box 117)
    - 1979 (Box 117)
    - 1984 (Box 117)
    - 1984-1987 (Box 117)
  - Forensic Studies Department (Box 117)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 117)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 117)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 117)
  - Forum Group INC. (Box 117)
    - 1986 (Box 117)
    - 1987 (Box 117)
  - For Your Information, 1973 (Box 117)
  - Foster Project (Box 117)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 117)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 117)
  - Foster International LLC, 1984 (Box 117)
  - Foundation for Economic and Business Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 117)
  - Indiana University Foundation (Box 117)
    - 1971-1972, (2 folders) (Box 118)
    - 1971, (3 folders) (Box 118)
    - 1972, (5 folders) (Box 118)
    - 1972-1973, (3 folders) (Box 118)
    - 1973-1974, (3 folders) (Box 118)
    - 1972-1974 (Box 118)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 118)
    - 1974, (3 folders) (Box 119)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 119)
    - 1975, (3 folders) (Box 119)
    - 1975-1976, (3 folders) (Box 119)
    - 1976, (3 folders) (Box 119)
    - 1976-1977, (2 folders) (Box 119)
    - 1977, (2 folders) (Box 119)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 119)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 120)
    - 1978, (3 folders) (Box 120)
    - 1977-1978, (2 folders) (Box 120)
    - 1979, (3 folders) (Box 120)
    - 1979-1980, (2 folders) (Box 120)
    - 1980, (4 folders) (Box 120)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 120)
    - 1981, (4 folders) (Box 120)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 120)
    - 1982, (2 folders) (Box 120)
    - 1982, (4 folders) (Box 121)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 121)
    - 1983, (5 folders) (Box 121)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 121)
    - 1984, (3 folders) (Box 121)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 121)
    - 1985, (2 folders) (Box 121)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 122)
    - 1986, (2 folders) (Box 122)
    - 1987, (4 folders) (Box 122)
  - Foundation at Fort Wayne (Box 122)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 122)
    - 1983, (2 folders) (Box 122)
  - Foundation at Fort Wayne (Box 122)
    - 1983, (2 folders) (Box 122)
    - 1984 (Box 122)
    - 1985 (Box 122)
    - 1986 (Box 122)
    - 1987 (Box 122)
  - Founder's Day (Box 122)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 123)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 123)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 123)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 123)
    - 1975 (Box 123)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 123)
    - 1977 (Box 123)
    - 1978 (Box 123)
    - 1979 (Box 123)
    - 1980 (Box 123)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 123)
    - 1981, (2 folders) (Box 123)
    - 1982, (3 folders) (Box 123)
    - Gift report, 1982-1983 (Box 123)
    - 1983 (Box 123)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 123)
    - 1984, (2 folders) (Box 123)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 123)
    - 1985 (Box 123)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 123)
    - 1986 (Box 123)
  - Fraenkel, Peter (Box 123)
    - General (Box 123)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 123)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 123)
      - 1974-1978 (Box 123)
      - 1977 (Box 123)
      - 1986 (Box 123)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 123)
      - 1974 (Box 123)
      - 1975 (Box 123)
      - 1976 (Box 123)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 123)
  - Franklin, Joseph A. (Box 123)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 123)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 123)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 123)
  - Fraternities and Sororities (Box 123)
    - General (Box 123)
      (See Box 262)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 123)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 123)
      - 1973-1975 (Box 123)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 123)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 123)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 123)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 123)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 123)
      - 1980 (Box 123)
      - 1981 (Box 123)
      - 1983 (Box 123)
      - 1984 (Box 123)
      - 1985 (Box 123)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 123)
    - Edgewater Conference, 1983-1984 (Box 123)
    - Kappa Alpha Psi – Fraternity Diamond Jubilee, 1986 (Box 123)
  - Freshman Induction Ceremony (Box 123)
    - 1981 (Box 123)
    - 1982 (Box 123)
    - 1983 (Box 123)
    - 1984, (2 folders) (Box 123)
    - 1985 (Box 123)
    - 1986 (Box 123)
  - Fringe Benefits (Box 123)
    - Insurance, Personal Accident, 1970-1973 (Box 123)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 123)
    - Automobile, Mass Merchandising, 1971-1972 (Box 123)
    - Review Committee, 1971-1974 (Box 123)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 123)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 123)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 123)
    - Review Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 123)
    - Long-Term Disability, 1972-1976 (Box 123)
    - 1975-1976, (2 folders) (Box 124)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 124)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 124)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 124)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 124)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 124)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 124)
  - Fullbright Awards, 1987 (Box 124)
  - Fulton, Anna May, 1977 (Box 124)
  - Fun Frolic (Box 124)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 124)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 124)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 124)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 124)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 124)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 124)
  - Fund Statements (Box 124)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 124)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 124)
    - 1982 (Box 124)
  - Fund for Theological Education (Box 124)
    - 1985 (Box 124)
    - 1986 (Box 124)
    - 1987 (Box 124)
  - Furnishings Policy (Box 124)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 124)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 124)
  - Future Studies (Box 124)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 124)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 124)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 124)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 124)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 124)
  - G, 1971-1987; (6 folders) (Box 124)
  - Gal, 1971-1987 (Box 124)
  - Gar, 1971-1987 (Box 124)
  - Gay Awareness Conferences, 1974-1976 (Box 124)
  - Ge, 1971-1987 (Box 124)
  - Geo, 1971-1987 (Box 124)
  - Gi, 1971-1987 (Box 124)
  - Gil, 1971-1987 (Box 124)
  - Gin, 1971-1987 (Box 124)
  - Gl, 1971-1987 (Box 124)
  - Go, 1971-1987 (Box 125)
  - Gol, 1971-1987 (Box 125)
  - Goo, 1971-1987 (Box 125)
  - Gor, 1971-1987 (Box 125)
  - Gos, 1971-1987 (Box 125)
  - Gr, 1971-1987 (Box 125)
  - Gran, 1971-1987 (Box 125)
  - Gre, 1971-1987 (Box 125)
  - Gri, 1971-1987 (Box 125)
  - Gro, 1971-1987 (Box 125)
  - Gu, 1971-1987 (Box 125)
  - Gary Income Maintenance Project (G-X) (Box 125)
    - October 1970-August 1971 (Box 125)
    - August 1971-December 1972 (Box 125)
    - 1973 (Box 125)
    - 1974 (Box 125)
    - 1975 (Box 125)
  - Genetic Research, 1976-1977; (2 folders) (Box 125)
  - General and Technical Studies (Division of) (Box 125)
    - General (Box 125)
      - 1971-1973 (Box 125)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 125)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 125)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 125)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 125)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 125)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 125)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 125)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 125)
    - Annual Report (Box 125)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 125)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 125)
    - Review Committee, 1974-1975; (2 folders) (Box 125)
  - General Electric Career Guidance Training, 1971-1972 (Box 125a)
  - General Electric Company Foundation (Box 125a)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 125a)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 125a)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 125a)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 125a)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 125a)
  - General Motors (Box 125a)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 125a)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 125a)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 125a)
  - Geology (Box 125a)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 125a)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 125a)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 125a)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 125a)